Begmuhommet Jumayev



begmuhommet.jumayev@gmail.com



+62081353877505



linkedin.com/in/begmuhommet



https://github.com/begmuhommet

Summary

I am a result-oriented Frontend Developer with 4.5+ years in the Web Development space. I focus on code quality, relevant technologies, and results. Since 2018 I worked as a freelancer as well as for several companies. I have experience working in a team as well as individually. I can manage both my tasks and the team's tasks. Experienced mentoring new developers.

Experience



Frontend Developer & Web designer

EktaChain

Jun 2022 - Present (1 year 4 months)

- Communication with the team: project manager, backend and blockchain developers.
- Design and development of blockchain web applications.
- Code review of backend and blockchain developers.
- Support for developed applications.

More than 7 blockchain projects have been developed.

Some of the projects:

- + Blockchain wallet: https://multi.ekta.io
- + Payroll control system: https://claim.ekta.io
- + Token swap: https://wekta-swap.ekta.io
- + Platform for selling NFTs: https://endorse.ekta.io

Stack used: Typescript, React.js, Next.js, MobX, MaterialUI, TailwindCSS, Wagmi, Ethers.js, WalletConnect

i-neti Frontend Developer

i-Neti

Aug 2021 - Jun 2022 (11 months)

- Communication with the team: project manager, backend developers, and designers.
- Development and support of web applications.
- Review of code from other front-end developers.
- Mentoring new developers.

More than 5 projects have been developed.

Some of the projects:

- + Platform for online learning: https://beztatarlar.ru/
- + Web application for the charity platform: https://podsolnukh-web.netimob.com/
- + Web application for reading and listening to the Bible https://mobile.i-neti.ru/projects/dom-izrailya

Stack used: Typescript, React.js, Next.js, MobX, MaterialUI, React Hook Form, Yup.

Frontend Developer

freelance.ru

Nov 2018 - Aug 2021 (2 years 10 months)

- Search for projects on the freelance platform.
- Communicate with customers.
- Project evaluation.
- Web application development.

More than 20 projects have been developed.

Some of the projects:

- + Application for viewing point clouds: https://tetravis.trimetari.com/
- + Service for the game CS:GO: https://fastmm.win

Stack used: HTML, CSS, JS, JQUERY, SASS, GULP, Vue.js, Vuex, React.js, Redux, Strapi

Education

30 Kahramanmaraş Sütçü İmam Üniversitesi

Bachelor's degree, Electrical and Electronics Engineering 2015 - 2019

Skills

TypeScript • React.js • Next.js • MobX • Redux.js • Material-UI • Tailwind CSS • Web3 • HTML5 • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS)